<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LatihanUTS3</string>
    <string name="name_ex">Cole Palmer</string>
    <string name="pos_ex">Midfielder</string>
    <string name="desc_ex">Cole Jermaine Palmer (born 6 May 2002) is an English professional footballer who plays as an attacking
        midfielder or winger for Premier League club Chelsea and the England national team. Known for his dribbling,
        playmaking and composure, he is regarded as one of the best young players in Europe.</string>

    <string-array name="player_name">
        <item>Cole Palmer</item>
        <item>Enzo Fernandes</item>
        <item>Joao Felix</item>
        <item>Mykhailo Mudryk</item>
        <item>Nicholas Jackson</item>
        <item>Noni Madueke</item>
        <item>Pedro Neto</item>
        <item>Reece James</item>
        <item>Filip Jorgensen</item>
        <item>Marc Cucurella</item>
        <item>Moises Caicedo</item>
        <item>Tosin Adarabioyo</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="player_desc">
        <item>Cole Jermaine Palmer (born 6 May 2002) is an English professional footballer who plays as an attacking
        midfielder or winger for Premier League club Chelsea and the England national team. Known for his dribbling,
        playmaking and composure, he is regarded as one of the best young players in Europe.</item>
        <item>Enzo Jeremías Fernández (born 17 January 2001), often referred to as simply Enzo, is an Argentine professional
            footballer who plays as a midfielder for Premier League club Chelsea and the Argentina national team. Primarily a central midfielder,
            he is also capable of playing as a defensive or attacking midfielder.</item>
        <item>João Félix Sequeira (Portuguese pronunciation: [ʒuˈɐ̃w ˈfɛliks]; born 10 November 1999) is a Portuguese professional
            footballer who plays as an attacking midfielder or forward
            for Premier League club Chelsea and the Portugal national team.</item>
        <item>Mykhailo Petrovych Mudryk (Ukrainian: Миха́йло Петро́вич Му́дрик; born 5 January 2001) is a Ukrainian professional footballer
            who plays as a winger for Premier
            League club Chelsea and the Ukraine national football team.</item>
        <item>Nicolas Jackson (born 20 June 2001) is a Gambian-born Senegalese professional footballer
            who plays as a striker for Premier League club Chelsea and for the Senegal national team.</item>
        <item>Chukwunonso Tristan "Noni" Madueke (born 10 March 2002) is an English professional footballer
            who plays as a winger for Premier League club Chelsea and the England national team.</item>
        <item>Pedro Lomba Neto (European Portuguese: [ˈpeðɾu ˈnɛtu]; born 9 March 2000) is a Portuguese professional footballer who
            plays as a winger for Premier League club Chelsea and the Portugal national team.</item>
        <item>Reece Lewis James (born 8 December 1999) is an English professional footballer who plays as a right-back
            for Premier League club Chelsea, who he captains, and the England national team.</item>
        <item>Filip Jörgensen (born 16 April 2002) is a Swedish-Danish professional footballer
            who plays as a goalkeeper for Premier League club Chelsea.</item>
        <item>Marc Cucurella Saseta (born 22 July 1998) is a Spanish professional footballer who plays as a left-back or
            left wing-back for Premier League club Chelsea and the Spain national team.</item>
        <item>Moisés Isaac Caicedo Corozo (born 2 November 2001) is an Ecuadorian professional footballer who plays as a
            defensive midfielder for Premier League club Chelsea and the Ecuador national team.</item>
        <item>Abdul-Nasir Oluwatosin Oluwadoyinsolami Adarabioyo (born 24 September 1997), sometimes known mononymously as Tosin,
            is an English professional footballer who plays as a centre-back for Premier League club Chelsea.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="player_position">
        <item>Midfielder</item>
        <item>Midfielder</item>
        <item>Midfielder</item>
        <item>Forward</item>
        <item>Forward</item>
        <item>Forward</item>
        <item>Midfielder</item>
        <item>Defense</item>
        <item>GoalKeeper</item>
        <item>Defense</item>
        <item>Midfielder</item>
        <item>Defense</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>